Excellent work on finishing up this case study!
You completed all major portions of the data analytics and visualization pipeline.
You went from data cleanup and exploration to identifying insights in the ecommerce dataset.
You built interactive dashboard-style pages for executives and provided specific business recommendations.
These final dashboard pages now help with communicating your insights.
The Whiskique executives can now easily explore key KPIs and
drill down into the details, such as sales, customers, and expenses.
This will enable the company to make more informed decisions about future cross-sell
promotions, logistics related to shipping items, and further ways to reduce their operating costs.
Congratulations on completing the case study.
We've covered many topics in this case study, from data
modeling to exploratory data analysis, DAX functions, and report design.
There's a lot more to discover with Power BI, and you are only just scratching the
surface, so be sure to check out some of the other Power BI case studies available on DataCamp!
Once again, congratulations.
Now, get out there and use your newly learned Power BI skills!